<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<SmellBaseline>
  <ManuallySuppressedIssues/>
  <CurrentIssues>
    <ID>InvalidPackageDeclaration:GitRemoteUrlUseCaseTest.kt:package com.lomo.domain.usecase</ID>
    <ID>InvalidPackageDeclaration:GitSyncErrorUseCaseTest.kt:package com.lomo.domain.usecase</ID>
    <ID>InvalidPackageDeclaration:StorageFilenameFormatsTest.kt:package com.lomo.domain.model</ID>
    <ID>InvalidPackageDeclaration:StorageTimestampFormatsTest.kt:package com.lomo.domain.model</ID>
    <ID>InvalidPackageDeclaration:ValidateMemoContentUseCaseTest.kt:package com.lomo.domain.usecase</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:CheckAppUpdateUseCaseTest.kt:CheckAppUpdateUseCaseTest$/* * Behavior Contract: * - Unit under test: CheckAppUpdateUseCase * - Owning layer: domain * - Priority tier: P0 * - Capability: manual app update checks return installable update info only for verified newer APK candidates. * * Scenarios: * - Given a newer release where the first APK candidate is unsupported and a later candidate is verified, when manual update check runs, then release notes and verified APK asset metadata are preserved. * - Given a verified newer APK candidate whose metadata version keeps the release-tag v prefix, when manual update check runs, then the update is still returned. * - Given a same-name APK candidate with a higher versionCode, when manual update check runs, then Android upgrade suitability is based on versionCode and the update is returned. * - Given a newer display version whose APK versionCode is not greater than the installed versionCode, when manual update check runs, then the update is rejected before install. * - Given a verified APK candidate without versionCode metadata and the installed versionCode is known, when manual update check runs, then the candidate is rejected as unverifiable. * - Given a verified APK candidate without versionCode metadata and the installed versionCode is unavailable, when manual update check runs, then versionName remains the compatibility fallback for old environments. * - Given a newer release without an APK candidate, when manual update check runs, then no installable update is returned. * - Given a same-version or downgrade release, when manual update check runs, then no update is returned even if the APK candidate is verified. * - Given a newer release whose APK candidate is unsupported because package metadata is wrong, when manual update check runs, then the candidate does not enter the install path. * * Observable outcomes: * - Returned AppUpdateInfo or null, selected version, release notes, APK download URL, file name, and size. * * TDD proof: * - RED observed with `./gradlew --no-daemon --no-configuration-cache --console=plain :domain:test --tests 'com.lomo.domain.usecase.CheckAppUpdateUseCaseTest'`. * - The v-prefixed candidate scenario failed because evaluateAppUpdate compared verified.versionName=`v1.1.0` directly, parsing `v1` as 0 and filtering a valid newer release. * - RED observed during this follow-up because the known installed versionCode plus missing candidate versionCode scenario returned AppUpdateInfo instead of null. * * Excludes: * - GitHub HTTP transport, APK download bytes, PackageInstaller intents, checksum/signature validation, and UI presentation. * * Test Change Justification: * Reason category: Contract hardening for update safety. * Old behavior/assertion being replaced: A force marker could return update info for the same version without an installable APK candidate. * Why old assertion is no longer correct: update discovery must not route same-version, downgrade, or unverified assets toward installation. * Coverage preserved by: release notes are still preserved in the verified newer-candidate scenario. * Why this is not fitting the test to the implementation: the new assertions encode the audit requirement that install paths only accept verified newer candidates. */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:CheckAppUpdateUseCaseTest.kt:CheckAppUpdateUseCaseTest$test</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:CheckStartupAppUpdateUseCaseTest.kt:CheckStartupAppUpdateUseCaseTest$/* * Behavior Contract: * - Unit under test: CheckStartupAppUpdateUseCase * - Owning layer: domain * - Priority tier: P0 * - Capability: startup app update checks honor the user preference and expose installable updates only for verified newer APK candidates. * * Scenarios: * - Given startup checks are disabled, when startup update check runs, then release/runtime repositories are not queried. * - Given startup checks are enabled and a newer release has an unsupported first APK candidate plus a verified later candidate, when startup update check runs, then release notes and verified APK asset metadata are preserved. * - Given startup checks are enabled and a newer release has no verified APK candidate, when startup update check runs, then no installable update is returned. * - Given startup checks are enabled and a same-version release is forced in release notes, when startup update check runs, then the force marker does not bypass version suitability. * * Observable outcomes: * - Returned AppUpdateInfo or null, repository call gating, raw release notes, APK download URL, file name, and size. * * TDD proof: * - RED observed during Batch 2C with `./gradlew --no-daemon --no-configuration-cache --console=plain :domain:test --tests 'com.lomo.domain.usecase.CheckStartupAppUpdateUseCaseTest'`. * - Before the shared evaluator was applied, startup checks could return update info for a newer release without a verified installable APK candidate and could let a force marker bypass same-version suitability. * * Excludes: * - GitHub HTTP transport, APK download bytes, PackageInstaller intents, checksum/signature validation, and UI presentation. * * Test Change Justification: * Reason category: Contract hardening for update safety. * Old behavior/assertion being replaced: Startup checks accepted force-marker release info without requiring a verified installable APK candidate. * Why old assertion is no longer correct: startup update discovery must not route unverified or same-version assets toward installation. * Coverage preserved by: raw release notes remain asserted in the verified newer-candidate scenario. * Why this is not fitting the test to the implementation: the new assertions encode the audit requirement that install paths only accept verified newer candidates. */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:CheckStartupAppUpdateUseCaseTest.kt:CheckStartupAppUpdateUseCaseTest$test</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:CredentialStateTest.kt:CredentialStateTest$/* * Behavior Contract: * - Unit under test: Credential state domain model * - Owning layer: domain * - Priority tier: P0 * - Capability: represent stored credential presence and read/validation failures without depending on provider code. * * Scenarios: * - Given a missing credential, when configuration state is queried, then it is not configured. * - Given a present credential, when configuration state is queried, then it is configured. * - Given an unreadable credential, when configuration state is queried, then it is not treated as missing or configured. * - Given an invalid credential, when configuration state is queried, then it remains distinguishable from missing. * - Given optional S3 stored credentials are unreadable, when aggregate state is queried, then provider readiness remains present while health is unreadable. * * Observable outcomes: * - StoredCredentialStatus values, their configured/missing flags, and provider readiness/health status. * * TDD proof: * - Fails before the fix because StoredCredentialStatus does not exist. * * Excludes: * - Android Keystore I/O, DataStore migration, provider UI coordinator state, and credential value material. */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:CredentialStateTest.kt:CredentialStateTest$CredentialFieldState(CredentialField.S3_ENCRYPTION_PASSWORD, StoredCredentialStatus.Missing)</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:CredentialStateTest.kt:CredentialStateTest$CredentialFieldState(CredentialField.S3_ENCRYPTION_PASSWORD2, StoredCredentialStatus.Missing)</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:CredentialStateTest.kt:CredentialStateTest$test</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:DailyReviewQueryUseCaseSeededOrderTest.kt:DailyReviewQueryUseCaseSeededOrderTest$/* * Behavior Contract: * - Unit under test: DailyReviewQueryUseCase * - Behavior focus: seeded random-review ordering must stay stable within the same day so a persisted page index still points at the same memo ordering after re-entry. * - Observable outcomes: identical memo id ordering for repeated queries with the same seed. * - TDD proof: Fails before the fix because the use case always reseeds from volatile time and exposes no way to replay the same random walk. * - Excludes: session date rollover, UI pager restoration, and repository paging correctness already covered elsewhere. */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:DailyReviewQueryUseCaseTest.kt:/* * Behavior Contract: * - Unit under test: DailyReviewQueryUseCase * - Owning layer: domain * - Priority tier: P0 * - Capability: page Daily Review as a typed memo collection source with bounded candidate chunks, stable memo identity, and random-walk continuation. * * Scenarios: * - Given a non-positive page size, when a page is requested, then no memos are returned. * - Given no memos exist, when a page is requested, then the collection page is empty. * - Given a session source with excluded ids, when a page is requested, then excluded ids never appear. * - Given the same session source and excluded ids, when a page is requested repeatedly, then memo ordering is deterministic. * - Given a large visible collection, when the first page is requested, then only bounded repository pages are read into the candidate chunk. * - Given more than one candidate chunk exists, when a new head memo arrives before the candidate phase finishes, then the new memo is not returned until the original boundary is exhausted. * - Given additions and deletions keep the same collection size, when a later candidate page loads, then new ids outside the original boundary are not admitted into the candidate phase. * - Given the backing collection grows after a session page, when the candidate snapshot is exhausted, then new visible unseen memos are returned deterministically. * - Given a seen memo is deleted and the collection grows, when the candidate snapshot is exhausted, then the deleted seen id remains excluded and the new unseen memo can append. * - Given a memo disappears after the first page, when the next page is loaded from the returned source, then the disappeared memo stays excluded for that session. * - Given visible memo order changes after the first page, when the next source loads, then the random walk follows the frozen memo id chunk and does not admit new ids early. * - Given a returned source, when the next page loads, then the persisted random cursor state advances instead of replaying from the seed head. * - Given an initial source, when a page returns memos, then the next source advances the random chunk cursor and accumulates seen ids. * - Given deterministic visible-unseen append fills before a repository page ends, when the next page loads, then unprocessed ids from the same repository page are not skipped. * - Given deterministic visible-unseen append sees mostly seen ids, when one page is loaded, then repository page scanning is bounded and the cursor advances even if no ids append. * * Observable outcomes: * - Returned memo ids, next source sessionDate, seed, excludeIds, randomIndexCursor, randomIndexSwaps, randomCandidateChunkIds, candidatePageOffset, observedMemoCount, pageSize, and repository call counters. * * TDD proof: * - RED command: `./gradlew --no-daemon --no-configuration-cache --console=plain :domain:test --tests 'com.lomo.domain.usecase.DailyReviewQueryUseCaseTest'`. * - RED symptom: `:domain:compileTestKotlin FAILED` with unresolved `randomCandidateChunkIds`, `randomIndexSwaps`, and `candidatePageOffset` fields before the bounded chunk source was implemented. * - GREEN command: same targeted domain command passes after the collection source freezes only bounded candidate chunks, persists cursor state, and scans visible unseen ids only after the snapshot chunks are exhausted. * * Excludes: * - UI pager rendering, repository storage internals, and full MemoCollectionPresenter integration. */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:DailyReviewQueryUseCaseTest.kt:DailyReviewQueryUseCaseTest$test</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:DailyReviewSessionUseCaseTest.kt:DailyReviewSessionUseCaseTest$/* * Behavior Contract: * - Unit under test: DailyReviewSessionUseCase * - Behavior focus: same-day session reuse, cross-day reset, and persisted page updates for the active random-review session. * - Observable outcomes: returned session date, seed, page index, and repository writes. * - TDD proof: Fails before the fix because random review has no persisted same-day session contract, so it cannot restore the previous page against a stable ordering. * - Excludes: UI pager rendering, DataStore key wiring, and memo query pagination. */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:DailyReviewSessionUseCaseTest.kt:DailyReviewSessionUseCaseTest$initialSession = DailyReviewSession(date = today.minusDays(1), seed = 42L, pageIndex = 7)</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:DailyReviewSessionUseCaseTest.kt:DailyReviewSessionUseCaseTest$repository.lastSavedSession shouldBe DailyReviewSession(date = today, seed = 123L, pageIndex = 5)</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:DomainPurityTest.kt:DomainPurityTest$withClue("Domain layer must stay framework-agnostic. Offenders: ${offenders.joinToString { it.path }}") { (offenders.isEmpty()) shouldBe true }</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:DomainPurityTest.kt:DomainPurityTest$withClue("Domain module must not apply Android Gradle plugins.") { (!text.contains("androidLibrary") &amp;&amp; !text.contains("com.android.library")) shouldBe true }</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:DomainPurityTest.kt:DomainPurityTest$withClue("Domain module must not depend on inject libraries.") { (!text.contains("javax.inject") &amp;&amp; !text.contains("jakarta.inject") &amp;&amp; !text.contains("libs.javax.inject")) shouldBe true }</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:DomainPurityTest.kt:DomainPurityTest.Companion$"""^(?:public\s+|internal\s+|private\s+)?(?:sealed\s+)?(?:data\s+)?(?:class|object|interface|enum\s+class)\b.*"""</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:GitSyncRepositoryDefaultsTest.kt:GitSyncRepositoryDefaultsTest$/* * Behavior Contract: * - Unit under test: GitSyncRepository default helpers * - Behavior focus: observeLastSyncInstant/observeLastSyncTimeMillis default mapping remains stable after repository surface cleanup. * - Observable outcomes: null-vs-instant mapping from the last-sync flow. * - TDD proof: Fails to compile before the cleanup because the old Git memo-history method is still required by GitSyncRepository. * - Excludes: sync execution, conflict handling, and any removed Git memo-history capability. */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:GitSyncSettingsUseCaseTest.kt:GitSyncSettingsUseCaseTest$/* * Behavior Contract: * - Unit under test: GitSyncSettingsUseCase * - Behavior focus: remote backend policy updates, Git settings mutation, conflict-resolution actions, and exception mapping semantics. * - Observable outcomes: backend policy writes, fake repository state, memo refresh count, and returned result mapping. * - TDD proof: Fails before behavior changes or migration are applied. * - Excludes: repository implementation details, network behavior, and UI rendering. */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:LanSharePairingCodePolicyTest.kt:LanSharePairingCodePolicyTest$(LanSharePairingCodePolicy.hasValidLength("x".repeat(LanSharePairingCodePolicy.MAX_LENGTH + 1))) shouldBe false</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:LanSharePairingCodePolicyTest.kt:LanSharePairingCodePolicyTest$/* * Behavior Contract: * - Unit under test: LanSharePairingCodePolicy * - Behavior focus: normalization, length validation, save-failure classification, and dialog-dismiss rules. * - Observable outcomes: normalized strings, Boolean validation results, thrown exception type, and user message keys/messages. * - TDD proof: Fails before behavior changes or migration are applied. * - Excludes: persistence storage, UI dialog rendering, and transport authentication. */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:LanSharePairingCodePolicyTest.kt:LanSharePairingCodePolicyTest$LanSharePairingCodePolicy.saveFailureMessage(IllegalArgumentException("")) shouldBe LanSharePairingCodePolicy.INVALID_LENGTH_MESSAGE</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:LanSharePairingCodePolicyTest.kt:LanSharePairingCodePolicyTest$LanSharePairingCodePolicy.userMessageKey(" Pairing code must be 6-64 characters ") shouldBe LanSharePairingCodePolicy.UserMessageKey.INVALID_PAIRING_CODE</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:LanSharePairingCodePolicyTest.kt:LanSharePairingCodePolicyTest$LanSharePairingCodePolicy.userMessageKey(" invalid password ") shouldBe LanSharePairingCodePolicy.UserMessageKey.INVALID_PAIRING_CODE</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:LanSharePairingCodePolicyTest.kt:LanSharePairingCodePolicyTest$LanSharePairingCodePolicy.userMessageKey("server unreachable") shouldBe LanSharePairingCodePolicy.UserMessageKey.UNKNOWN</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:MemoContentAnalyzerTest.kt:/* * Behavior Contract: * - Unit under test: MemoContentAnalyzer * - Owning layer: domain * - Priority tier: P0 * - Capability: provide a single domain-owned memo content analysis contract for query/filter decisions. * * Scenarios: * - Given markdown todo syntax, when content is analyzed, then todo presence is reported. * - Given markdown image, wiki image, or audio markdown references, when content is analyzed, then attachment presence is reported. * - Given http, geo, mailto, or raw email references, when content is analyzed, then URL/contact presence is reported. * - Given plain text, when content is analyzed, then no content flags are reported. * * Observable outcomes: * - MemoContentAnalysis boolean fields returned from a content string. * * TDD proof: * - Fails before implementation because MemoContentAnalyzer and MemoContentAnalysis do not exist. * * Excludes: * - repository SQL, UI filtering, markdown rendering, attachment loading. */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:MemoIdentityPolicyTest.kt:MemoIdentityPolicyTest$/* * Behavior Contract: * - Unit under test: MemoIdentityPolicy * - Behavior focus: base-id construction, collision suffix/index resolution, timestamp offset clamping, and base/collision matching. * - Observable outcomes: generated ids, selected collision index, offset timestamps, and match Booleans. * - TDD proof: Fails before behavior changes or migration are applied. * - Excludes: memo persistence and parser behavior. */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:MigrationUseCaseTest.kt:MigrationUseCaseTest$/* * Behavior Contract: * - Unit under test: migration import/export use cases. * - Owning layer: domain * - Priority tier: P0 * - Capability: migrate all memo files/media and encrypted settings through stream-based archives. * * Scenarios: * - Given a workspace with notes and media, when all notes are exported, then the repository writes to the caller stream and returns item counts. * - Given a notes archive, when it is inspected before import, then the repository returns the manifest plan without rebuilding workspace state. * - Given a notes archive, when it is imported, then files are restored and current workspace state is rebuilt before returning. * - Given an encrypted settings file and a wrong password, when import runs, then the password failure remains observable. * * Observable outcomes: * - Bytes written to an output stream, returned migration summaries, returned dry-run plan, rebuild call count, and thrown exception type. * * TDD proof: * - RED: this spec fails to compile before migration repository and use cases exist. * - RED: dry-run plan spec fails before migration archive inspection use case and repository contract exist. * * Excludes: * - ZIP entry format, encryption primitives, Android URI picker wiring, and repository storage internals. */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:ParseRemindersUseCaseTest.kt:/* * Behavior Contract: * - Unit under test: ReminderMarker + ParseRemindersUseCase * - Behavior focus: parse the `@YYYY-MM-DD-HH:MM[xN][iM][rR][.done|.k]` token from memo content into structured ReminderMarker values. * - Observable outcomes: list of markers with dueAt, repeatCount, firedCount, intervalMinutes, recurrence, done, tokenRange, raw text. * - TDD proof: fails because parser does not extract recurrence and intervalMinutes. * - Excludes: scheduling, notifications. */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RemoteSyncSettingsSharedTest.kt:RemoteSyncSettingsSharedTest$/* * Behavior Contract: * - Unit under test: remote sync shared settings helpers in RemoteSyncSettingsShared.kt * - Capability: Backend-agnostic settings orchestration for Git/WebDAV/S3 remote synchronization. * - Scenarios: * - Given a configured RemoteSyncSharedStateObservation, when observing sync properties, then it should expose the flows correctly. * - Given a RemoteSyncSharedMutation, when updating sync enabled, then it updates backend type and reapplies policy. * - Given a RemoteSyncSharedMutation, when updating auto-sync properties, then it updates through provider and reapplies policy. * - Given a RemoteSyncSharedMutation, when updating sync on refresh, then it updates without reapplying policy. * - Given a RemoteSyncSharedActions with real SyncAndRebuildUseCase, when triggerSyncNow is called, then it triggers manual sync on the active provider. * - Observable outcomes: exposed flows, backend policy writes, auto-sync policy reapplication, and delegated manual-sync/connection-test results. * - TDD proof: Fails before behavior changes or migration are applied. * - Excludes: repository transport behavior, provider-specific field mapping, and UI rendering. */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:RewriteReminderTokenUseCaseTest.kt:/* * Behavior Contract: * - Unit under test: RewriteReminderTokenUseCase * - Behavior focus: replace one marker token in content with a new canonical token, preserving text around it; advance fired count; mark done. * - Observable outcomes: returned string with the targeted marker substituted exactly once. * - TDD proof: fails because RewriteReminderTokenUseCase does not yet exist. * - Excludes: persistence, scheduling. */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:S3SyncSettingsUseCaseStrongCompatTest.kt:S3SyncSettingsUseCaseStrongCompatTest$/* * Behavior Contract: * - Unit under test: S3SyncSettingsUseCase * - Behavior focus: S3 settings orchestration must expose and mutate the full rclone crypt configuration contract, including password2 and filename strategy fields. * - Observable outcomes: fake repository state, credential status checks, and observed rclone configuration flows. * - TDD proof: Fails before the fix because the use case only exposes the coarse encryption mode plus a single password field. * - Excludes: S3 transport behavior, codec internals, and UI rendering. */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:SearchMemosPageUseCaseTest.kt:SearchMemosPageUseCaseTest$test</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:ShareTransferErrorPolicyTest.kt:ShareTransferErrorPolicyTest$/* * Behavior Contract: * - Unit under test: ShareTransferErrorPolicy * - Behavior focus: canonical error construction for pairing, attachment, connection, transfer, and unknown failure paths. * - Observable outcomes: emitted ShareTransferError code/detail/device fields for each policy entrypoint. * - TDD proof: Fails before behavior changes or migration are applied. * - Excludes: UI string presentation and LAN transport behavior. */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:ShareTransferErrorPolicyTest.kt:ShareTransferErrorPolicyTest$ShareTransferErrorPolicy.attachmentTooLarge() shouldBe ShareTransferError(code = ShareTransferErrorCode.ATTACHMENT_TOO_LARGE)</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:ShareTransferErrorPolicyTest.kt:ShareTransferErrorPolicyTest$ShareTransferErrorPolicy.attachmentsTooLarge() shouldBe ShareTransferError(code = ShareTransferErrorCode.ATTACHMENTS_TOO_LARGE)</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:ShareTransferErrorPolicyTest.kt:ShareTransferErrorPolicyTest$ShareTransferErrorPolicy.pairingRequiredBeforeSend() shouldBe ShareTransferError(code = ShareTransferErrorCode.PAIRING_REQUIRED)</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:ShareTransferErrorPolicyTest.kt:ShareTransferErrorPolicyTest$ShareTransferErrorPolicy.tooManyAttachments() shouldBe ShareTransferError(code = ShareTransferErrorCode.TOO_MANY_ATTACHMENTS)</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:ShareTransferErrorPolicyTest.kt:ShareTransferErrorPolicyTest$ShareTransferErrorPolicy.transferFailed() shouldBe ShareTransferError(code = ShareTransferErrorCode.TRANSFER_FAILED)</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:ShareTransferErrorPolicyTest.kt:ShareTransferErrorPolicyTest$ShareTransferErrorPolicy.unsupportedAttachmentType() shouldBe ShareTransferError(code = ShareTransferErrorCode.UNSUPPORTED_ATTACHMENT_TYPE)</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:StartupMaintenanceSyncInboxStructureTest.kt:StartupMaintenanceSyncInboxStructureTest$/* * Behavior Contract: * - Unit under test: StartupMaintenanceUseCase * - Capability: Guarantee recreation of sync-inbox directory structure before processing inbox files on startup. * - Scenarios: * - Given a startup request, when running deferred startup tasks, then it first ensures the sync inbox directories are created, and only then processes pending inbox sync changes. * - Observable outcomes: Ordering of ensureDirectoryStructure and UnifiedSyncOperation.PROCESS_PENDING_CHANGES. * - TDD proof: Fails before behavior changes or migration are applied. * - Excludes: filesystem creation details, cache warm-up behavior, and conflict dialog handling. */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:StartupMaintenanceSyncInboxStructureTest.kt:StartupMaintenanceSyncInboxStructureTest$val initializeWorkspaceUseCase = InitializeWorkspaceUseCase(directorySettingsRepository, mediaRepository)</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:StartupMaintenanceUseCaseTest.kt:StartupMaintenanceUseCaseTest$/* * Behavior Contract: * - Unit under test: StartupMaintenanceUseCase * - Capability: Safe cold-start optimization, deferred maintenance sequencing, cache warmups, and version-change cache invalidation/resync. * - Scenarios: * - Given workspace config, when requesting root directory, then it maps and returns the raw root directory path. * - Given an unchanged app version, when deferred startup runs, then it warms the image map cache and skips resync. * - Given a startup request, when deferred startup runs, then it recreates the inbox directory structure before processing changes. * - Given a changed app version but missing root directory, when deferred startup runs, then it updates version without full resync. * - Given slow image cache warmup, when deferred startup runs, then it processes sync inbox changes concurrently without blocking. * - Given failing rebuild or image cache refresh, when deferred startup runs on version change, then it swallows failures best-effort and finishes. * - Given generic sync inbox failures, when deferred startup runs, then it continues executing best-effort. * - Given a sync inbox conflict, when deferred startup runs, then it rethrows the conflict for UI-level resolution. * - Observable outcomes: call counts, state changes, version updates, thrown exceptions, and execution concurrency. * - TDD proof: Fails before behavior changes or migration are applied. * - Excludes: repository implementation internals, filesystem or network integration, and UI rendering. */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:StartupMaintenanceUseCaseTest.kt:StartupMaintenanceUseCaseTest$/* * Test Change Justification: * - Reason category: test framework migration &amp; optimization * - Replaced assertion: Removed all coVerify/verify MockK checks. * - Previous assertion is no longer correct because we migrated completely to pure state-based fakes. * - Retained coverage: All BDD scenarios and assertions on observable side-effects are completely preserved. * - Why this is not changing the test to fit the implementation: The contract of StartupMaintenanceUseCase remains exactly as specified. */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:StartupMaintenanceUseCaseTest.kt:StartupMaintenanceUseCaseTest$val initializeWorkspaceUseCase = InitializeWorkspaceUseCase(directorySettingsRepository, mediaRepository)</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:StartupMaintenanceUseCaseTest.kt:StartupMaintenanceUseCaseTest.&lt;no name provided&gt;$override suspend</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:StartupMaintenanceUseCaseTest.kt:StartupMaintenanceUseCaseTest.&lt;no name provided&gt;$override suspend fun allocateVoiceCaptureTarget</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:StartupMaintenanceUseCaseTest.kt:StartupMaintenanceUseCaseTest.&lt;no name provided&gt;$override suspend fun ensureCategoryWorkspace</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:StartupMaintenanceUseCaseTest.kt:StartupMaintenanceUseCaseTest.&lt;no name provided&gt;$override suspend fun removeVoiceCapture</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:StartupMaintenanceUseCaseTest.kt:StartupMaintenanceUseCaseTest.&lt;no name provided&gt;$override suspend fun setRemoteSyncBackend</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:StorageTimestampFormatsInvisibleSeparatorTest.kt:StorageTimestampFormatsInvisibleSeparatorTest$/* * Behavior Contract: * - Unit under test: StorageTimestampFormats * - Behavior focus: memo header parsing when invisible separators appear before the leading dash or between the dash and timestamp token. * - Observable outcomes: parsed header presence, parsed time token, and stripped content remainder. * - TDD proof: Fails before the fix when a UTF-8 BOM or zero-width space prevents `- HH:mm:ss` memo headers from being recognized. * - Excludes: file loading, markdown rendering, and memo repository orchestration. */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:SyncAndRebuildUseCaseTest.kt:SyncAndRebuildUseCaseTest$/* * Behavior Contract: * - Unit under test: SyncAndRebuildUseCase * - Capability: Sync orchestration and coordination across Git, WebDAV, S3, and Inbox sync backends. * - Scenarios: * - Given a configured Git backend, when running non-force sync with cancellation, then it is rethrown and refresh is skipped. * - Given a configured Git backend, when running force sync with failure, then it refreshes and rethrows the failure. * - Given a configured WebDAV backend, when running force sync with error, then it refreshes and throws the mapped WebDAV exception. * - Given a configured WebDAV backend, when running force sync with cancellation, then it is rethrown and refresh is skipped. * - Given a configured Git backend, when running non-force sync with failure, then it fails silently best-effort and refreshes anyway. * - Given a configured WebDAV backend, when running non-force sync and WebDAV is disabled, then it skips remote sync and refreshes. * - Given no backend, when running force sync, then it refreshes without triggering any remote sync. * - Given a configured Git backend requiring direct path, when running force sync, then it refreshes and throws direct path required error. * - Given a configured Git backend with conflicts, when running force sync, then it refreshes and throws SyncConflictException. * - Given an unconfigured WebDAV backend, when running force sync, then it refreshes and throws not-configured error. * - Given a configured Git backend, when running non-force sync and Git sync is disabled, then it skips remote sync and refreshes. * - Given an unconfigured S3 backend, when running force sync, then it refreshes and throws S3 not-configured error. * - Given a configured S3 backend, when running non-force sync and S3 sync is disabled, then it skips remote sync and refreshes. * - Given a configured S3 backend, when running non-force sync and S3 sync is enabled, then it triggers optimized S3 sync and refreshes. * - Observable outcomes: thrown exception type, refresh execution, and collaborator call counts / state mutations. * - TDD proof: Fails before behavior changes or migration are applied. * - Excludes: repository transport internals, remote network request details, and UI rendering. */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:SyncAndRebuildUseCaseTest.kt:SyncAndRebuildUseCaseTest$/* * Test Change Justification: * - Reason category: test framework migration &amp; optimization * - Replaced assertion: Removed all coVerify/verify MockK checks. * - Previous assertion is no longer correct because we migrated completely to pure state-based fakes. * - Retained coverage: All BDD scenarios and assertions on observable side-effects are completely preserved. * - Why this is not changing the test to fit the implementation: The contract of SyncAndRebuildUseCase remains exactly as specified. */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:SyncConflictResolutionUseCaseTest.kt:SyncConflictResolutionUseCaseTest$/* * Behavior Contract: * - Unit under test: SyncConflictResolutionUseCase * - Capability: Unified conflict resolution and side-effect coordination across distinct remote sync backends. * - Scenarios: * - Given a GIT conflict set, when resolved successfully, then it invokes resolve on the GIT repository and refreshes memos. * - Given a GIT conflict set, when resolve fails with an error, then it maps the error to GitSyncFailureException and skips refresh. * - Given a WEBDAV conflict set, when resolved successfully, then it invokes resolve on the WEBDAV repository and refreshes memos. * - Given a WEBDAV conflict set, when resolve fails with an error, then it maps the error to WebDavSyncFailureException and skips refresh. * - Given an S3 conflict set, when resolved successfully, then it invokes resolve on the S3 repository and refreshes memos. * - Given an S3 conflict set, when resolve returns pending, then it returns a pending resolution result and skips refresh. * - Given an S3 conflict set, when resolve fails with an error, then it maps the error to S3SyncFailureException and skips refresh. * - Given a NONE conflict set, when resolved, then it skips remote resolver invocation and refreshes memos directly. * - Given an INBOX conflict set, when resolved successfully, then it invokes resolve on the INBOX repository and refreshes memos. * - Observable outcomes: thrown domain exception type and payload, resolver invocation path, and refresh invocation count. * - TDD proof: Fails before behavior changes or migration are applied. * - Excludes: repository implementation internals, network/filesystem behavior, and UI rendering. */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:SyncConflictResolutionUseCaseTest.kt:SyncConflictResolutionUseCaseTest$/* * Test Change Justification: * - Reason category: test framework migration &amp; optimization * - Replaced assertion: Removed all coVerify/verify MockK checks. * - Previous assertion is no longer correct because we migrated completely to pure state-based fakes. * - Retained coverage: All BDD scenarios and assertions on observable side-effects are completely preserved. * - Why this is not changing the test to fit the implementation: The contract of SyncConflictResolutionUseCase remains exactly as specified. */</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:SyncConflictResolutionUseCaseTest.kt:SyncConflictResolutionUseCaseTest$S3SyncResult.Error(code = S3SyncErrorCode.BUCKET_ACCESS_FAILED, message = "bucket failed", exception = cause)</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:SyncConflictResolutionUseCaseTest.kt:SyncConflictResolutionUseCaseTest$WebDavSyncResult.Error(code = WebDavSyncErrorCode.CONNECTION_FAILED, message = "connection failed", exception = cause)</ID>
  </CurrentIssues>
</SmellBaseline>
